Faculty Women's Club. Sections. Annual reports. 1925-2000.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Sections. Annual reports.
1925-2000
University Archives Record Series 79
UCLA Library Special Collections
3.6 linear ft. (9 Boxes)
Record Series 79 contains the annual reports generated by officers and sections of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 79 contains the annual reports generated by officers and sections of UCLA's Faculty Women's Club.
Boxes 7-9 are pending description.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3521011
- Annual reports - officers'., 1925-1930. (Box 1, Folders 1-5)
- Annual reports - officers'., 1932-1954. (Box 1, Folders 6-26)
- Annual reports - officers'. (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Annual reports - officers'., 1954-1962. (Box 1, Folders 28-35)
- Annual reports - officers'., 1962-1976. (Box 2, Folders 1-14)
- Annual reports - officers'., 1976-1993. (Box 3, Folders 1-17)
- Annual reports - officers'., 1993-2000. (Box 4, Folders 1-7)
- Annual reports - miscellany (board supplies). (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Annual reports - sections'. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Annual reports - sections'., 1927-1957. (Box 4, Folders 10-36)
- Annual reports - sections'., 1957-1980. (Box 5, Folders 1-23)
- Annual reports - sections'., 1980-2000. (Box 6, Folders 1-18)